PINBALL HAZARD
It's not what I think it is?
Seriously? Underwear?
Framed underwear?
Have you ever seen that?
No, it's definitely a first for me.
Oh!
It's so dark.
It's starting to feel like a trap.
Oh.
I've seen those before.
I find this interesting choice
of decoration, rather poetic.
Not another click!
Were we not just talking about traps?
I was actually talking about poetry.
I thought I'd gotten us in a pickle.
That sound...
I swear I didn't do it!
All right. I think the coast is clear.
It was just to turn on the lights.
Whenever you say something,
the opposite happens?
I know.
This isn't going to be good!
This isn't good at all!
You good, Ruel?
You know me. I'm not the type
to complain for no reason...
but right now I won't lie to you,
I'm not feeling great. I feel awful.
I just heard my body cracking in places
where it usually doesn't.
Hey, guys.
Yet another weirdo.
A collector!
A collector, little girl, not a loony.
Too young to understand.
I am Black Bump, the Feca demigod,
and this place is my humble home.
He looks pretty strong.
I assume you know who we are
and your orders are to slow us down?
Slow you down?
I've heard a lot about you,
but nothing about being funny.
No one leaves without my consent.
I could do far more than that!
No point wasting time,
we already know how this will end.
Calm down. I'm not like the others.
I follow no one
and I am willing to let you pass.
Really?
Yes, just as long as you all pay the toll.
Pay the toll!
We're not paying for anything!
The little one's right.
The tightwad is awake.
You take care of him while I recover.
The living proof of masculine bravery!
We'll see if you're still so hot-blooded
at my age.
We don't have any valuable items.
You have your underwear!
Anything but that...
Everybody has a pair of underwear
and that's just what I want!
What do you think?
It's our chance to escape.
We don't know what's there
and with my big belly--
I'll protect you, Ma.
He cannot be serious!
Is the crossing fee too pricey for you?
Many consider it cheap.
Not pricey, absurd!
Maybe to you, but not to me.
No way.
Not yours, child.
Do you think I'm some kind of pervert?
I want theirs.
Mr. Stroud's underpants
will be displayed here,
in the pantheon of the greatest riches.
He will be ranked seventh.
Seventh? That's it?
Yes. Our young friend, Yugo,
will be placed among the rare Eliatropes.
And the cherry on the cake,
I'll be able to add a new princess
to my collection.
He is a total animal.
As for you, you don't deserve to be
in my very exclusive collection yet.
Mr. Bump, I really don't care
about any of that.
-Just give him it and we can get going.
-What?
She's got a point. I've been meaning
to change my underwear for 25 years.
I don't mind going commando,
so I won't miss them.
For once, I'm okay with paying up.
Are you delirious? If you seriously think
that I'm going to give him--
You're mistaken.
We won't give you anything.
If you want it, come and get it!
It would be my honor.
The rules are simple. See these two poles?
Combined, they form the key
that will get you out of here.
This shouldn't be hard.
Yugo!
Yugo, are you okay?
I'm fine. It's just going to be
a bit harder than I thought.
I'd rather die than give him anything.
What a tragedy.
You should be honored
that I'm asking you.
My collection contains boxers and panties
from the crème de la crème of Krosmoz.
Intimacy is the path to the soul.
What's more intimate than underwear?
Having all these fragments of souls
fills me with joy,
because I know I'm the guardian...
of a magnificent temple.
And I will not tolerate blasphemy.
A force field surrounds him.
He doesn't need any armor.
This won't be easy.
Papa likes opponents like him
who don't show their weak points
until you find them.
What would Papa do?
-I know!
-Elely!
He would have gone
straight into the fight.
Foolish little girl!
He would have taken a few hits
to test the waters!
Are you going to fight like a man,
or hide behind your shield?
You are pathetic!
You guys see that?
This dummy isn't untouchable.
Hey, little know-it-all,
I've told you, I'm not interested in you!
Elely!
I'm not really sure if copying your dad's
fighting style is the wisest choice.
You should just... find your own.
It's the family style.
It always pays off in the end!
Move aside. I'm going to make a portal.
It seems you haven't figured it out yet.
Nothing in the world can get
through my force Bumpers.
It doesn't matter, Yugo.
I found his weak point, when he attacks...
He needs to turn off his force field.
I noticed too, thanks to you, Elely.
Sadlygrove style! Take a few hits
to find out where it hurts!
Dally would be proud.
Don't encourage her like that, Yugo.
Amalia, Ruel, let's show this clown
what we're made of!
We'll make him shake
in his tighty-whities.
He's going to soil his pants!
You stupid fools!
So you've been wearing
the same underwear for 25 years?
I inherited them from my grandpa!
Oh, that's wonderful.
-No!
-Ruel!
Now the next!
You bunch of chumps! I don't know
what you thought you saw before,
but my force fields have no weaknesses!
This room is designed so that I can defeat
anyone who enters,
without using any weapon.
Amalia...
As for you, your panties will be placed
in the "stuck-up princess" category.
Don't touch her!
-You okay, Amalia?
-Yeah I'm fine.
Well done, you've exhausted
what little patience I had.
You're about to see what kind of surprises
this room hides.
Prepare yourselves!
A rolling sound.
It's... coming from the walls.
Merrily they roll along...
Doesn't the void ever call out to you?
Not the void you're talking about.
Echo?
How do you always spot me so easily?
I want to know your secret!
He says "Echo" every five minutes
and sometimes you're actually there,
so it gives the illusion
he can see everything.
If Adamai gives all my tricks away,
I'm done for.
Our guests are with Bump.
They're advancing quickly.
Evangelyne and Flopin are waiting
in the Eniripsa temple.
Perfect. Soon it will be time for Flopin
to reveal his potential to us.
We can't win. It's never-ending.
You can't give up hope yet!
I've figured out a solution.
I just saw one ball rebound
and crash into the floor.
It's the only part without a force field.
If you can get them to bounce downwards,
you might get rid of them.
That sounds like a plan.
They keep bouncing back and forth.
We need to get them rolling faster.
I could try to make ramps.
The more speed they pick up,
the more of a risk they'll be to us.
We'll get through this. We always do.
Let's do this, then. Make them go faster
when they're rolling towards him.
Wretched fools...
Now, Amalia!
So you want some more?
Behind me!
My temple...
No!
What a commotion!
Amalia, you risked your life for me.
If you hadn't, I'd be...
You've done the same for me
so many times.
One thing's for sure.
You're not as dumb as I thought.
And you two are just so cute.
You should have stayed in your hole!
All alone, little Eliatrope.
We'll see who's little!
I hope you're not flat out.
What did you expect, kid? I'm a Feca!
My armor was only amplifying
my force fields.
Stop calling me that! I'm not a kid!
You again.
We aren't finished yet.
I... just wanted...
...to have your underpants.
Awesome fight, Yugo!
I didn't know you could fight like that!
Yeah, me neither! Thanks, Ruel!
I owe you one.
It was my pleasure, buddy.
Let's see what's next.
Yugo... That was amazing.
Don't you think it's time for us
to admit how we feel about each other?
You know that it's impossible, Amalia.
Nothing's impossible.
No, don't! It will never work between us.
I might or might not grow up,
but I don't want you to wait for me.
I've barely changed after all these years.
Yeah, maybe, but inside,
I know you're a man.
Don't make me doubt. It just won't work.
But you're the one who kissed me!
Yeah, I know. It was a mistake.
I could never give you
what you want from me.
It was a mistake?
You kissed me by mistake?
You selfish jerk! Did you even think
about how I might be feeling?
As if things weren't complicated enough...